[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1990 movie contains the following exchange: \n-Get me out of here. \n-There is no out of here. Youve been killed, dont you remember??", "correct_answer": "Jacobs Ladder", "incorrect_answers": ["Lord of Illusions", "It", "The Tommyknockers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dry air consists mostly of what gas?", "correct_answer": "Nitrogen", "incorrect_answers": ["Carbon Dioxide", "Oxygen", "Argon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is Egg Island located?", "correct_answer": "Bahamas", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "Hawaii", "Mexico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Remember George: No man is a failure who has friends is the beginning of an inscription in a book given to George in the movie Its a Wonderful Life. What is the rest of the inscription?", "correct_answer": "Thanks for the wings", "incorrect_answers": ["Its a wonderful life", "Did you hear that bell?", "Hold your friends close"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If we had to measure the width (i.e. the diameter) of a single human hair in carbon atoms, how much would this width be?", "correct_answer": "1 million carbon atoms", "incorrect_answers": ["1 thousand carbon atoms", "1 billion carbon atoms", "100 thousand carbon atoms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following materials is the densest?", "correct_answer": "Iridium", "incorrect_answers": ["Gold", "Aluminum", "Platinum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In No Country for Old Men, how much money was in the satchel Moss found at the crime scene?", "correct_answer": "2 million dollars", "incorrect_answers": ["6 million dollars", "586, 000 dollars", "a million dollars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Alien film was not nominated for an Oscar in any category?", "correct_answer": "Alien Resurrection", "incorrect_answers": ["Aliens", "Alien", "Alien 3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before becoming US President in 1981, he was head of a labor union.", "correct_answer": "Reagan", "incorrect_answers": ["Hoover", "Truman", "Johnson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What island, located in the North Pacific Ocean, is also known as the Big Island?", "correct_answer": "Hawaii", "incorrect_answers": ["Cuba", "Haiti", "Maui"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately what percentage of Americas waste is paper?", "correct_answer": "39 %", "incorrect_answers": ["14 %", "8 %", "24 %"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Silk", "incorrect_answers": ["Wooden", "Steel", "Lace"]}]